shatteredcrystal.com 2010-06-16

# Privacy Policy

| 

Privacy Policy

By registering, you will open an account with Markee Dragon INC (MDINC) in the United States. Your data will be stored in the USA. Though MDINC may share your data with MDINC affiliates in countries with varying personal data protection laws, your data is always protected by our Privacy Policy. MDINC and MDINC affiliates use your data to administer your account, provide information of interest to you, and to communicate with you. You may opt out of receiving marketing materials by changing your account preferences to exclude administrator emails for our forums and by writing [support@trustwho.com](mailto:support@trustwho.com) letting them know you wish to never receive any promotional emails. More information about how MDINC uses your data and your related rights can be found in our Privacy Policy below. By registering, you agree that MDINC may process your data in accordance with the following Privacy Policy and that you will abide by Terms & Conditions below.

MDINC ONLINE PRIVACY POLICY: MDINC and its subsidiary companies respect the privacy rights of our online visitors and recognize the importance of protecting the information collected about you. We have adopted a corporate wide Online Privacy Policy that guides how we collect, store and use the information you provide online. This policy applies to all MDINC owned sites. To view a complete list of these owned MDINC Web Sites, please visit [http://www.markeedragoninc.com. ](http://www.markeedragoninc.com/)In addition, MDINC owns several other domain names that resolve to the web sites listed above. We may also add new sites that are subject to this privacy policy and we may update this list to include those. Please note that this policy applies only to sites maintained by MDINC and its subsidiaries, and not to web sites maintained by other companies or organizations to which we link.

#### Third Party Sites.

If you click on a link to a third party site, including on an advertisement, you will leave the MDINC site you are visiting and go to the site you selected. Because we cannot control the activities of third parties, we cannot accept responsibility for any use of your personal information by such third parties, and we cannot guarantee that they will adhere to the same privacy and security practices as MDINC. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of any other service provider from whom you request services. If you visit a third party website that is linked to an MDINC site, you should consult that siteâ€™s privacy policy before providing any personal information. 

#### What is personal information and when does MDINC collect it?

Personal information is information that identifies you and may be used to contact you on-line or off-line. MDINC collects personal information from our online visitors during (1) contests (registration or claiming a prize), (2) warranty registration and/or during customer support or technical service requests, (3) member match up or other online services, (4) registration for forums, (5) newsletter subscriptions, referral services, and other marketing surveys and email campaigns, (6) registration for membership on our sites, (7) when you order products or subscriptions from us online, or (8) when you request services from third party service providers on our site or (9) through use of our software or online services. 

Information collected will vary depending upon the activity and may include your name, e-mail address, phone number, mobile number, home address, birth date, and credit card information. In addition, we may collect demographic information such as gender, zip code, information about your computer, hardware, software, platform, media, Internet IP address and connection, information about online activity such as feature usage, click paths and other data that you may provide in surveys or online profiles, for instance. We may combine demographic information with personal information, such as email address, to tailor our offerings or web pages to your preferences or interests. Affiliates or prize winners may also be required to provide Social Security or Social Identification Number for tax purposes. We do not require personal information to obtain access to any of our sites; however, you will not be able to access areas that require registration. 

If you wish to subscribe to our newsletter(s), we will use your name and email address to send the newsletter to you. Out of respect for your privacy, we provide you a way to unsubscribe. 

If you choose to use our referral service to "tell a friend" about an MDINC product or site, we may ask you for your friendâ€™s name and email address. We will send your friend an email on your behalf inviting him or her to visit the site or check out our product. MDINC stores your friend's name and email for a short period for the sole purpose of sending this email and for redundancy checking, to be sure that your friend does not receive multiple copies of the same email message. We do not keep or use this information for any other purpose. Whatever the purpose may be, we will only collect information to the extent reasonably necessary to fulfill your requests and our legitimate business objectives. 

#### MDINC's Online Stores

Visitors purchasing goods and services through one of our online stores may need to provide a valid credit card number and expiration date, in addition to name, mailing address(es), phone number and e-mail address. Some of MDINCâ€™s online stores may employ third-party contractors whose opt-out instructions for promotional or marketing communications may vary from our own. 

#### Job Postings

MDINC allows for the online submission of resumes and employment related information. Please note that the information (including personal information) collected and services related to the online job application process are not subject to this privacy policy. However, we want to assure you that information obtained from our job site will be used solely for the purpose of accepting and evaluating your submission for possible employment and the related purposes described on our jobs site. 

#### Online Chat Rooms and Profiles

You may choose to disclose information, including personal information, about yourself in our online chat rooms, message boards, user â€œprofilesâ€ for public view or in similar forums on our sites. Information that you disclose in any of these forums is public information, and there is no expectation of privacy or confidentiality there. You should be aware that any personally identifiable information you submit there can be read, collected, or used by other users of these forums, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in these forums. 

#### Public Data

Your participation in our online sites or events, is conditional upon you agreeing to us collecting, using, storing, transmitting and publicly displaying statistical data (such as your scores, rankings and achievements) generated through your participation. 

#### A Special Note about Children

MDINC does not knowingly collect data from anyone under the age of 13. We have blocks in place to prevent anyone under the age of 13 from creating accounts on all of our sites. The only exception to this is with written parental approval. 

#### What about cookies and other technologies?

We use cookies and other technologies to passively collect demographic information, personalize your experience on our site and monitor advertisements and other activities. Cookies are small files downloaded to your computer to track movements within web sites. We may link cookie information to personal information. Cookies link to information regarding what items you have selected for purchase at our store, pages you have viewed, or games you have played. This information is used to keep track of your shopping cart and make sure you don't see the same ad repeatedly. Also, we use cookies to deliver content specific to your interest and to monitor website or game usage. We collect information on what forums are visited, how much time is spent and which ads or links are clicked.. Some of our sites use an outside ad company to display ads. These ads may contain cookies. Cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad companies, and MDINC does not have access to this information. Most browsers are automatically set to accept cookies whenever you visit a website. You can disable cookies or set your browser to alert you when cookies are being sent. However some areas of our sites will not function properly if you do so. Please note that this privacy policy covers the use of cookies by MDINC only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers. 

MDINC also maintains log files which contain Internet Protocol ("IP") addresses. An IP address is a numeric address that is assigned to your computer by your Internet Service Provider. In general, we only use log files to monitor traffic on our Web sites, to report aggregate information to our advertisers and to troubleshoot technical problems. In the event of user abuse of our websites, however, we may block certain IP addresses. IP addresses may be used to personally identify you in order to enforce our Terms of Use. 

We may use third party contractors, such as credit agencies or market research firms, to supplement personal information that you provide to us for our own marketing and demographic studies, so that we can consistently improve our sites and related advertising to better meet our visitors' needs and preferences. To enrich our profiles of individual customers, we tie this information to the personally identifiable information they have provided to us. 

When our third-party contractors collect and/or have access to the personal information you provide to MDINC, MDINC requires that they adhere to our stated privacy policies and protect the confidentiality of personal information they collect or have access to in the course of their engagement by MDINC. These third parties are prohibited from using your personally identifiable information for any other purpose without your specific consent. 

#### Where is the information held?

MDINC is a global organization and many of the computer systems on which MDINC collects, stores, and uses the information it collects or receives are based in Europe, the United States and elsewhere. Your personal information may be transferred to, used, processed or held by MDINC in the United States and in other countries, including countries both in and outside the European Union, and used for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy. 

#### Safeguarding Your Personal Information

The security of your personal information is important to us. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card number and/or social security number) on our registration or order forms, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. 

By using this site, you signify your assent to the MDINC Online Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use any MDINC site. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the home page, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page. If you choose to opt-out of our changed practice, our e-mail will contain instructions on how to opt-out. Your continued use of our site will signify your acceptance of the changes to our Online Privacy Policy. 

|    

Support

» FAQ's  
» Resend your codes  
» [Email](mailto:support@shatteredcrystal.com)

Policies

» Payment options  
» Returns  
» Defective Codes

Contact

» About Us  
» Contact Information

Affiliates

» Learn about the affiliate program \- Make money from visitors to your site by referring their business to us.  
» Join the affiliate program and generate income from your site!  
» Login as an Affiliate  
» Affiliate Banners

Sites we like

» [FreeGameCam](http://www.freegamecam.com/)  
» [Markee Dragon](http://www.markeedragon.com/)  
» [TrustWho](http://www.trustwho.com/)  
» [UO Brokers](http://www.markeedragon.net/)  
» [Live MMO Support](http://www.livemmosupport.com/)  
» [Shattered Crystal Blog](http://gametimecard.blogspot.com/)
